The 4th film by Quentin Tarantino. Uncut, unrated, and shown in its entirety.
Kill Bill: The Whole Bloody Affair is a action, crime
film directed by Quentin Tarantino.
A former assassin—known only as The Bride—wakes up from a coma after her former boss and lover,
Bill, shoots her in the head and steals her unborn child during her wedding rehearsal.
She soon embarks on a bloody quest for revenge, hunting down her ex-colleagues of
the Deadly Viper Assassination Squad before confronting Bill himself.
Quentin Tarantino’s complete Kill Bill, a combination of Volumes 1 and 2, previously deleted scenes, alternate takes, a
full-color remaster of the Crazy 88 fight, a 7-minute anime sequence by Production I.G., and a built-in intermission.
The Bride / Beatrix Kiddo (Black Mamba) / Mommy, played by Uma Thurman.
O-Ren Ishii (Cottonmouth), played by Lucy Liu.
Vernita Green (Copperhead), played by Vivica A. Fox.
Budd (Sidewinder), played by Michael Madsen.
Elle Driver (California Mountain Snake), played by Daryl Hannah.
Bill (Snake Charmer), played by David Carradine.
Kill Bill: The Whole Bloody Affair is a 2006 American martial arts
film written and directed by Quentin Tarantino.
It combines the films Kill Bill: Volume 1 (2003) and Kill Bill: Volume 2 (2004),
which were conceived and produced as a single film, but split in two.
Uma Thurman stars as the Bride, who swears revenge on a group of
assassins after they try to kill her and her unborn child.
Kill Bill: The Whole Bloody Affair premiered at the Cannes Film Festival in May
2006 and screened at Tarantino's New Beverly Cinema in 2011.
Tarantino said he had waited until he owned the rights before giving the film a full release
and thought that asking audiences to come to his theater gave it more meaning.
It was theatrically released in the United States by
Lionsgate on December 5, 2025, to critical acclaim.
The film explores themes of martial arts, kung fu, revenge, aggressive, absurd.